[{"topicId":"17","id":"17000","langCode":"vi","question":"mX4n8f3CUn3BpuW9kilc0YiDL4+FjyWPREML4ski+WehhzG+5/AzXMiMIsTsnSMDAMoF64MWTyLHTIlm9cNqzw\u003d\u003d","answers":["are watched","is watched","has been watched","is being watched"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3OYGBzJp7Yj/Q1yGRh07qNAAHJAjqACPEaYUfvMwRQGB/YrSrrmUeROBX3lQNIT6jJaRk+IQMrhdtonXJL5WWn0/lqaS+2q4T6b/iC1ONCIJWS9s/bKsVaFmbhcYpYmCCNdqKrokIHrpHtzlgabErmWrEcCc62JPsMeDXJ3O9W7kxjknrVHbvlUXs7bLuMLyVI9oy5Iq7w057kcpzZB0CBHoRYgGpE2rnTkZrFGIfNSkWy14dZVcq79hqUqZCa9ztAcvlvL3VV5kwr2wx23Op9CBW+5vURSkoZb1w1bikcwhtB+nNX2aUvSCAUUax/URyiVFWCvFPvmNYGbGnL6SDyjS/EME4faMrWaia+OTVqMEzu+U5PyperDTVTKCylNBLc2iFfeKokBXqr4RQIFiFnrVpOQxPDZrWefgxDs97F8pz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz6A4sx5FYMXg6o6ZQEG43RvMozNL74WjM+JBTOMvH34LJlceuplmJjufX6TcXuYciXiZ3KL9iyMdfygUfobxPPx6txYu2w8E3QFZemgrvfVqg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17001","langCode":"vi","question":"Yp/pPgTgyzSgmeg8U2PuYMr9dBGzcsENuxwVOqciqyI\u003d","answers":["paints","are being painted","is being painted","painted"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwAYle03urMZ3kLmkerPxgt4K5pCOtp479eeP2jA8p2mL4AslFnM7ytb8bAwclJX+6Yggz2rSLs/+lXB7+83NqL1Ih5cDcxImed0wI11S3ewSZeio17o9N0U5f/qpEiX2JSjkO91LVj/Ws/ZKnvprmkX3TXREk7br910UkadaM1ZDUe00Xj4pxZHofp03JUtX7LNnaP8jVYGC48fC022HchpJ+ZMqFqQ3amj35QOieLt147TZ94Lt9UbQgIeuNGet2J4lWk5Sd4UUMZFJjDYRY1MfOS09GJqfmTpGmkI7sGwLJvcjngC0VnwlqT5cVetCQsxsSaSeVjTjQ/7suuDwGRbbgIctrWW4A4KWtxuvSRd77Xeg4VONmnZQnwGRAHGm2n+CfTYAqfecm4Zg3uAOpszB49ZaNE03UikUhbPjsj60Gel9K9qzFTzQb+dBCu3c4Mp8D+hLynVRoeBfgnyAiNQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASau5rz/JF+TKk6NQt0ZfDHrW9TAnFylXUNiw1GOndW0k4pWCeB5dXr66wm5SGe8UJ2bVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17002","langCode":"vi","question":"hNJGCDYOeSGxnLfIIzCgDYIojm2BQf8qIIbZyMSTOqfmrDaAUyr1rjSgQMrdjRN/C01Z7AstaVaoVvbsWmYGeg\u003d\u003d","answers":["was published","are published","publishes","published"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7VdJI9LINUbn/iSWAlqpjWNS6sY/ZUnlkjwnJrH3cjumyY33bHu5ltnVCqJAohlh3+0hah8dFgZMQwcVp2HL2UXzSlfK8DQ1zDhmbFWwD507IhxWr02Phhec8FJluaEa0E98UGorXn+k+/6xUtiv1g35o83XyMdCY0+VL/8Ruqq3uekri7zsF704l3R4QXL4K4d5rvjGO5wljymWT3v2OfY5GrsHlBX79nxnve4kak8bL3VHAra8L/CZ9YcplD0K2+LDIXb8nXPuqa8q2YLH+OH+3Uvyum6A4S+cKwc/XhtpRtsyE3xZO1dkDWS0e7CRtSTNOOH7NffHLTxt31Wj2LMq1zh/P0rwOxw70WHsHmThut1zvj5/jLqaa1JJeMYxJ7iUz8AibKpRwqXNa3yFuo04F1YlzQwyQAc1DS0r5wX45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/O0tErFt1mwtJ/vy2CtziT63ZR60SHN9ZMc6etrBSByo/VK3XNfSX5Ux2jhoYa/HEXsVC5e7WMDAv1HgUmttbFiIJ05HQDx5N/hFnmIKZnuBK+98+PqthYZtG0oEpWhBQJvpDiXZxZoJRRE/HFpetaHcB2wR5Q05jHIxS6hsngMO"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17003","langCode":"vi","question":"rvEk9teiouBQcaen0kCWt/aTUL3MK+kEPNvDbvnnxT+U4qaxZ4iYgO8B3A6k8LHgqtJPs8xqdN1qjaR2TEDSZg\u003d\u003d","answers":["was being barked","were barking","barked","were being barked"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE79b2xt+b5ib/fAAhskhsRvRvurCcSbxO73njjnVZxVXJtYcD7bR8ug1E31xTYEkox9E7cfYIE1AejS7zmjcEitoK9vmHrhOalA2MYs+pexKQD3uXhtvVGKi+punIBmwQBK98p6gGmOp0dMjCO9PzjBwLgvrMr9GoDh6VxHKeqsKPCU7UbwuNDz2J99j9BgQrsYs0TMsmW4hph1dYV+uJgFNoXZ4C94nPBeO6F1QL75qBv7SMoSCQW6wFyUSfY+uf6YB11ep7jSoAKWb3fu704br4qEDOKputWqnhGHoo+muhJjHCoe5wVU8VXLa21/psr1m+WFQ2Ca4v/OKTyApsxmeJHTw0yAfOn6oRaartkfJ7gisHxxB/wPABeICtF1RDG6DUBMi21Zkbqhm1t2pqgrwx9RWB2+T7857CwG5zK8zFtNwMYt85gyb8voUJejz8Wsyuxi7Yjlb8Y/1IAlmcNJvdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99MJ43aC5j1Y8Jqpw+vCe/E61TMI2of8xqd0IQx3o+jf1fK5E5ec7MvdySCUM8+1hln+0FZxJZmk9RKJeDteBRnTY2s8Pjxc12KcNP/tJLq8AMIxEq2j91zNiyYQHHOPwyZHokQAuyMri5s26NX9NRHceyCJqI+hTlqdiIbCh3yp0o\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17004","langCode":"vi","question":"796wKKC9BwFzdZEwCidQsb5XakKHBUo8s9fwt3HWcJrhYhw8jtqhae4d4tg1vX7b","answers":["paid","hasn’t been paid","have paid","hasn’t paid"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0L2SIiHVhMiISXmDoCDojJDKt9bw2Skcq7c4s/2IfDEpa6V2ykOV3TsI7zdNtpul3yqwEllwOd4V56GgdT8fQ936Tdlltd2qzOJf7vKoplbE4FPHKylrCOSWRGcF0kYpZt6964I06iB1Twgu7utjG+i45Vvmh2qdIZgiJSjiQklLqZOzaJ+2ETqFdfO4J6TVVVcaxvDHV92yYEOim6Q8gU79AE+0G8v6DPKXuPMKR/NmX7d48F4uu6iRkJEmy6p+nQcJCfaALWNojnVppqp8YtnUvR7h8dnbpklF6y+5svIk1SDX+vwwt1hWfGH8CRafw8x1ztJJ/kOKBVMVR5wKpKkofuyvFJhLRj4K8HVS+5b5GMwwfJfMRtsxJcN1yTN8wzUOGDBJKo64uPtZG6DT7UN3e/D5l3u+8DFBk1oAGfRQgVvub1EUpKGW9cNW4pHMIbQfpzV9mlL0ggFFGsf1Ect1H5Qyy6bVdPrDKtGom/Mke2JLAWhX3Rimnl/zArAnR5QAppXmj1q/RK6DEg2V6sum4Uj3CeB2JZOPFjP2q0oABBgpz6mwP8Xx+8q/l5FO4Mp8D+hLynVRoeBfgnyAiNQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASap2OQXrgTzp35qoB+/fcM9KB3ImzL9ngAhHD9Ed1J672bunS1fK8WI+TKwF4omtGsSVr+NQEloUjPO6/tFBHkFxFQDqZaUTZ3DwF4IDYQbTT"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17005","langCode":"vi","question":"EnovdZGXg/xRUpmu5dQlyu8ycUG4ejGwsjtJETO/noPQ/GjiT8pJkYH8y9KUXz3uP2ruT3WhOx5x0hgPcz1EdQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["will replace","will be replaced","will replaced","replaced"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE054Ow96ZlPi7422GpC08YQfifxwlmVATPTaxw6B5nFuL4AslFnM7ytb8bAwclJX+6Yggz2rSLs/+lXB7+83NqL1Ih5cDcxImed0wI11S3ewSZeio17o9N0U5f/qpEiX2JSjkO91LVj/Ws/ZKnvprmnIuAh2hbM9fi1z0XIlFcdQkBs03u8iA7uZiS5CSjl5hDFNeU8TFFeRQQg3c3kjodtCELyIwmscH3cd7dhpLPYMUj2jLkirvDTnuRynNkHQIEehFiAakTaudORmsUYh81JR8ADDmSkQblnJjGCJ+7Rgb4sMhdvydc+6pryrZgsf44f7dS/K6boDhL5wrBz9eG2lG2zITfFk7V2QNZLR7sJG510vT6fLXIdOTU937V5jm/keYVoeqtdjK9ihq+4U97Ytve8c5bXrBONMeyZ655aZOl5d6QE+iHQzLEiwpogpo0UnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59QK8SudRL/+6qtgR+oDIyRXNyw3IROaxrd/HQvQgI7TXMf1lbGk/0SKxVFIdSdD2C+Qqm96zm5j4EAFsn/cSAcs1cp+JpsDykRLl6mSprQflEd8jw+MaPx56z8/vt0Zo3EeLLOr+Kq9VvxuDYIje95g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17006","langCode":"vi","question":"vf/hVyn3GP/RqOwq9xQNtxadBXwVRDqkEy7lxomq6zIDb5Ofmfo3MyxHJGwdAhY0RSmCQAf1xLPeIlIZOuavFg\u003d\u003d","answers":["will be being played","will played","will be played","will play"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE054Ow96ZlPi7422GpC08YQFgww6iaMbzne6ij9S2zB1YjLWMb8lTWoY0JQfDM1r5sJMm6Ej9cP9JeGGPGcfSMInVuHleziiZFOnzcdz9NPIn1dbMa8O3Dae4iKbUotsiV927cyJFOepAJ5rRpUO5NmOpN5qHhUPR9RzIqTvNbS13rOvgTNQIcQ6oYzpDxPAspiOCigqCIWSUJU4fOG2FtaVXZqqeYO0Rgv1vMqdTgtdzUOnc1XYND5fD18TXGj7bvkIK80fvNwv1AwOqMveZ4XyQDJkqusHxLEdRSaZyikAtRiIyzwce5f/uv69soi1hrLzasMxEvgn4DNPS5Qofz2VXZqqeYO0Rgv1vMqdTgtdzUOnc1XYND5fD18TXGj7bscP4B3yK2Zq5LwQam4VKvBvHDU8HkTG3yaA9rGLhFLNoj9q/Cno0WI6D2zDKsbCaUt9U35zGuNXbzoSp43c1rspGCsv8nNp6FJUNLoOsdtQIvPM5ZBU39xurHTszTciAhACZYGfY/nstD714Sp+pXZJtdsM/5jZkanO0ik2PhoTq7xTXl91sjA3Cp5VlZ9D3KAtCCPOinLf/PRqTGSmKUAlJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXH3quOhvL5QVl35hn2DO/JXzfPLfShMe7ZFXjxH1ErXSLqTdICQ+OhH7rGZgfPlBd6QN2+pMmt4+/XcpTvfi+AK7ri0g1Da+5ARIzNv8ioAKmeo5ldh6bPjKiQUFSybz1tVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17007","langCode":"vi","question":"YydM2VlS6Ed/mc7i8hSxDAjB/E9EIqD0c1Ue9lCbcRiEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["have been finished","will have finished","finished","will have been finished"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE22zg30IYASJznwWXYSsIszrmdO5O6cnHn3lfUzNWknKgoFUJWK9drLF9PkTl3FldpYbjtZSvnah+Rng8CbkCHJ41W7TLyxVxT7Gv3aNCt5XaLwZymj2qU6IBhMrqbYzPv5hsy6MjNB8Clhtggh30djUNoGRrvnvQuaKJbX1JlPIJEHkjYBH1FKDZ/GMQALO7BVc1Tw6cCmGe0JtSwN5NgE+xNYYYVXV8axxBWQa5U4/HGGSwQvLS4HyBvaOtjqViShR+sN1tZkoCm94f5YFrir6vBxJSRnCIavbcD8fEOV8z8UIsDxUEz12Gtbt5lSDxE7MHAlFAh7EhEhL6gE0hUwMIU+VxLxAZCwYYUVJDzjARHGsfAQnIpBJ6IXICCW1btf/K5XXYrjNYKR+qRvm5kEyF+A3EkJhmy0LHfGRzAKaN3SntN4iM7/LY/Ce3rc/MeJbrYE9zT9zgSPxY/ytNt2YqCCz3Es6l00DopoOjUFg+rwcSUkZwiGr23A/HxDlfLrUf6tdYv44VA0rrdhM2WlJtdsM/5jZkanO0ik2PhoTL9H+oIash0IamUiA1k1mWTrk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDq9q1HQZxkT03daiars3FNt3Y2Hyh1X6tBx+PKJDgpypg+Oa3D0AnRW35PryyaBhBiiv3F7fdfBYee/fgNh4TKTTWmLfgRBw+Qek5o2YnFfk3xhjHpPer77kOqcylug/rg\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17008","langCode":"vi","question":"8NzVn8cjWl9bfv6W6RMOpfS1iJ8vqFWKj0iuTvMjGnKyUb1GxEiRftznqJOcWUZq","answers":["took","is taken","to be taken","to take"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExPB+n7fYHVQNSK3Nv7nNiMQrJrPshlCfyuALuR2ZR1FRafUTmWNgeHrP6D3E+NX+BwTybqGcieNKU31KFTHKJsK0HVdZomZGDQAuzycL4yxVtskyjnzx7nP3o4YN8SvZYJB7ODAprVmcY2vXvn0tRK5E1AZ22Oilq8RLhAun5CxEedCPyPJFsOl6OombDTNlGr7445UkLM6S2zwZOgmu+Y2zUXF3wl5hsGaJODROVIXR9LQNeFdMzo6hA/la8kXl3/cfdsZFC150zbX1nBeS9mSZDLZ+tZzPkBt3nassQ3sMKmT14Mqu6BMFtXOqXOQP6Fow0QUHVkXf1K9o+BYaTgL+MMBy7oul/1TQ87GNps/fWNOqULhOrGscOuicTbMQ2kvrSsbxYNbmVP5LzYetEWeLM3+4seKsxwAH5ArOyUTVmdcdiJ2qk+ZWRw4JgvDWBAUNBN447DEriI7EB2uowzT6UVBYe8u+7464tyRVTQ2LrupLdv29+kc5AqUYWrJ07YlEjmm6am+b/G5yBQWtExbLaAHApBdlnBAOYuDvDSupsSsLGtdYdwSiBFlp5FKjArO/y7zeOPEm9sG8L6ycPId2N+s4jKLoUkuvtqAjThLJPuFrGBRMgLgRpbamna1BGdK5TZ1THtSr9QwPEpFUCSr82SmAFDS8Dw3GhSrr3IjB9LVcma6UmaZZBTHWtXjd19K7PBw+Q010ogJsTmIQJz/l4nHL1v6+b+L2YPprTMHuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuItpBpV8SMkZUB3TCJaAWecHnNlmYqPWgKcszTmXBcKrr47DaY6iQkyHcMzquJDNV58TeNWRjDdGoRTf5fEco4K+Jg7x+xLvWfeFvSPoX96og\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17009","langCode":"vi","question":"p6QDyYxz0WAwO/OmNuBJQUuycDxdPIIrNw1TFa8NPYzIa/y0TDHcAnhKtUKDk/3M","answers":["find","to find","found","to be found"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4yh6oYXrjsmEQAyiVypqJThd3C1KfNw6D7x60cweTGJDgwO/cBzyfQhLghlDgKUOu/Glr8jb3nq7o7dSRLbBKBf+gRhdF7/jI+7JSwsxVay583+XMqiVWWWV2il3TQTWPlYcuiqKxRdwfUfUDy2yuQkztmoQnZGSbLCkm+i2qQtP4hEw1NelIYxtGGF50nz+rSjRpTZmGmypTFcfMbYCGyuf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2JOjjL1zShP5UugUEZgCL7AFIhUdB5Zfg8CfvwS31GY9L0JCtoq+b1Znk53lEqGvCSvWW7LHNfrG5BYfXtOhXUblS0S2CY5STR3x0ULJKqfoOmTzwRyyXGKN/1QQRTMwZtPUzBfFrN15D1sSlfuQ5mbLmH96dRCwbgMwhPhRRvm4Sv0RdbqnJ3nY7jczXNziMB8jwUrVkoUEvYUCUA8qat6IaD7U35tqvqAvI92BeMN8//MenIwOsp+GaW2jq6Acsww4N4vn52y5hL256mmEc8EtP5NjwJDgh5t7JR9AneB9vmS2sP7w/MSj94vsgO/209bUfROlBsuVumIgfoXX8gTpEz8UpqcqFiIb0FsMAbZ6iSRCupMUcRBlnlYWT1S0W6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4lGcpkY1U4NNTd4S6A7MmZogc8kmSx0dTtFd5NVZGO1dH/suipBXvrpb5qcSJ56anwDWPE59B01sinBWFqwGCUxsEnXjUBLh1RhvC2H1dzJ5jUm3Q7qcC0naVXsJtPWvTM\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17010","langCode":"vi","question":"GpumxlAZKyIzMyUz7rmEsJtSpTLcS+N31vjK6OutEXE\u003d","answers":["to be prepared","to prepared","prepared","to prepare"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2L7LiVTI76kABiVkZyTLehr5qiDC6CTnD659LbOYM9x0ts0P/mwVvSgeqMd+l5aNcBr9yI+XGYuuvhw1vomU7XvrRg/M6T/HcODxf5KCHLfxwnYYnNZhVDnw6nxs0uWYuN/G5MBeUo+vql4YYwvT44OJ0cPUwWQFtNChG7dJGgvtbAnoCLCNe5lvyDhj8M/mLSjRpTZmGmypTFcfMbYCGyuf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2JOjjL1zShP5UugUEZgCL7BVR6KBu+N/crTIe4v4gcxP39G83B5cGwKzIVKkF2M4A1S3V9AAynygj4VulhJbU71+Tyw4Twjs3InzcSXZPd/WZpV46dB3bbK69x0qQfIic5x5ozR/W5DUf0HppkcTWna69qsDY7/XlhGB6tOulMkvF06O0/QxQOtOahzvWL5JqS39lgUM+m0/DfzC3IrOg6QhmU1PLzsxa8aTEZMTr+HlQpReq/rgsXM5F7c34bsWlkJZ5rlDf5mI+yjp2wnyc9SqDJqolmmKNOol1471+c8yyuG/ZOU1iBlijXzKw0Ef1D+OqVTQsSuYRKHKBr1RNzpZcfWgT1MKdTOK3+SqXzoMYxelReAeG5B/rviW7esSMh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8XfdM+NWlmTxL2ZqATCs9KKlGeDKVr5KEOFBd7XGkcBKVeCzMR4sPuWG4rQhYmL9hYmqvJGZRJNHz3ljkBqhtTdLk6fqdRgb9WaMvgMzKuNuLwL02VVO3uUaOiu2uIY7d8\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17011","langCode":"vi","question":"tqERU3AB/1wm7jHmhdN5d2IxZ/z0A6m6wfcLE0sKVIqOMQ37fABK56ueR2vYRkMW","answers":["called","to call","to called","to be called"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7IL45IL9167XvRhdc1U9qXoTJbhdGbB4D0vFcXIa7Mu2FUa57Cn5JSI9HqGavfk6Sus+P8rJYh+1VmiGEkhUklf+gRhdF7/jI+7JSwsxVay583+XMqiVWWWV2il3TQTWPlYcuiqKxRdwfUfUDy2yuStonDAkQzuSunTyYFPS7dOGgzGY3sYFGabumLLoEinWjuCAEWVgA+IgYJkvsXmpymj3j+bePF33M+bdZ6couqT3zqNzCv+vRNdjmbNFk9MXC82XUZ16kQ2Aqzv/cUaRqwI7FLaobi8KY+nri3mDsDWr4WGu/6F+x1eZXKNc9HMmoG4b4BowcZYGwU87ubEMXn1tR9E6UGy5W6YiB+hdfyBv8cptMjMBig/qN8+gl2cdWf9NQM8wI8tNS/XYv2S54YvuhCaQDMY4+Dh9nwcoPU+HKPECEOv0ylO2eD7yMgAQZIWbNDlDGAICtdrk1TMyxLapfKZ2wC9dHEVlDg8KOpqoB+NGlMXqi9paYmtLHl/dyDSXJOAm4WzcstQ5w43uTV11wgG+5LZtSgMEj6zsK5RKL2k7HHgCWl/EArsE56u7BvF1LN8+FmGLd+jQGn25RSDKfA/oS8p1UaHgX4J8gIjUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmqxBafuc1c+6i/pafFBKOIF7u8R+XEyS1Ymi3J6K1lp1kYezHLcXThYcW+XeMvXBAo3hvqkhFJbo/O0P1TLZCIg"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17012","langCode":"vi","question":"PFpjInokHwUYQkJ+FL/S+x1xqVPK1cCN5ZSUQHPobC8b0dKZE/IXD0dTP/oYbXHei2Sz28EZLCzLpzAexvpYzA\u003d\u003d","answers":["be paid","paid","paid","pays"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+/9t/VR0Bmsw8ELOmFUwxLIRJkO2yxx0PIMdkFvl4kxUZ6Ej6We1obCjMYeCmnlXkcDhh0eus09tsLhAUrEGonEtLXHIwWL5hoZmG1vGKK7OZhQSPCH1R4ETnSdfJxwFeX0NVB6NqmuU0V/EIybrWAAEXkX/Fxk0ti8TahEqELuWwsOmMmEcLdRXxnevX+9FcL7sCar0xg33JEbpS2mNMSAw42+T/4MVCrWT6GknQYYZMmIzd8jyhDO6CDmG4fuDCUm9CA4AaiSwk74xXu6bNdWpaMtgmyMLxWpxIWfykqdqbMXHNs+ptfy464X4zQO/il0WToSqoBI/eJEEWuY9B6p1iurJRyWQrI2zGtL9jHfrWW7YrBRjnW88BAc3xgb1nrIuTOLf6+91swzDpu+X0Y\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17013","langCode":"vi","question":"geNNXmogpl5NrbgdVolk0cDjjKD0CRILOMcUiCrJ2Fg8jHKG9N+nV1WWJSKZJSPY4FM3KepnzkXZbXWfciaUHg\u003d\u003d","answers":["be given","give","given","gave"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/yQCLAQLQgRbMSOAbs8S+lbcEuYFSXjrzNSgSHwraVndL+8qi+hhPI9PsGlSWDWowsxsSaSeVjTjQ/7suuDwGTDZHt71f8Qt3pXKSSV2Bpqw+UEnPkZdFcJlvL5VulW76DvQ/dufqKs+bcqt65VisOD71ArGtfT2lt0ozfjAYobtvMRRztv+QREe3XPSxSaJZ9Th5B1YFkFbA5oxn2Y3ZvNtraIBchSMnWoRjENEGdopkHSUGax1eCxgEpn/YDPWCuvvGM9x+3SHCxo0ON0CCKAw42+T/4MVCrWT6GknQYYZMmIzd8jyhDO6CDmG4fuDCUm9CA4AaiSwk74xXu6bNfCVrwA5lyMrDEjUaXfFHmyErWo+EwV6uLMmimzFy4ULVmAiOo/B6Neqp5bPLS0goEcC6WcjsYdaV3vaN6vz6ylhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17014","langCode":"vi","question":"8zszExqNm/PFr7Mr1Rxe7Qscxin+SkyP0KQJ0/TmHtY\u003d","answers":["be obeyed","obey","obeyed","be obey"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzobA4gndc+dxboaCII5crASryb4TpUsiKjVWBVoHJvFHSpmhp15MY5oyOYF0W6vpGfBPehh6PuJgVGm2bvg99TlJziaDXDs6pk/QyFGH24xyN3LfzeCUjdbtFMISGUKBEvFHYlyd55dZxByQxBPkyOPFwcNw5uOfAbljJT1xCQ/hQEBQoSIYST7NfgyO11c8eX0NVB6NqmuU0V/EIybrWAAEXkX/Fxk0ti8TahEqELuWwsOmMmEcLdRXxnevX+9FSshFbU+32K8M6rXlLcutHDuTl539L3GvIAedV0I6FG3RK57gUke+cE0tdvqZXfT9ac9HZkcdOgoHNY0AxgBI1bSrUevi5AH4beBuKXViL8+yBDZA1EOBFoUvmZJ3vypeCXd4buFhOphJzJ2tbUNpnPTKFlD8JrQIecM/Wne6GMv92fqsPFTLs9+MOcoIQS+lw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17015","langCode":"vi","question":"dsGnSHA5O5mTmM9tLQq4d9m+YZD5LWHEKPuBUcdQks3yRGJBs+6MTp6EuAN3gC2VdX3Fxz/zODocvcVy92fNfQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["cutting","be cut","cuts","cut"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9HOmHxEAIbLbSO5f6P+kl5px6vDeqE9f0eLDANe2uTUpntubiX/+14MoE/BKpUY9YmxsVoi3auicwO2tEWlvxqB45eAGuOw623DXMki7l8csGMFIqU5Xo5uZmV4qjnmw7mwi9zAqvr/aj/B/6aKtPH60TaUueNUjnsJAnrTAHPQhTJD3Ah8OGwycrnXAQU3fYGS5HNJbZopw4V/IreFEEF893/O30nIKU96fS8JUXmGxmgKqL+dewOipaJ9BDPXzrtagJvasUlKWc/ML2rJBMsqaI6jYYf9ZDQZkJ6JM93hPJTXj38Jhd2/ZOAtaIqPVdg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29htPysOd+whUrgrCYSqW5sK9cfVEy1xST4I+y/afF7DQU9dA2RQeQhOY6rT+ebzRfoFN8CSlTJpRdA0BNrkQeVzqys6AuAXWufBPxw1zwUwP8pkf7vqGIf6d3+6FtVREc\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17016","langCode":"vi","question":"EhtvLAS3HET0AXXYzYQ+OrJRIa0bemde88QZlWp7KmiGd/OSKQuQRg/DuLc7vLBm","answers":["be sent","to send","send","sending"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5mTZAyEcibPthI2BjDBA5cfgqWjV9qWDkNVIhuSTG/8jHoyZRkRSqbHewKAEfL7/UOV0Ih2ALFftPbVj3p05OyfB9qaomSh9vshK+BTX24j5grYFvkw8A4FVAWPKrTd5ARd+zB8ObAvsZN3i9XIghl3ql6Unp+3FgNbM4hjmrth7nj9FwZ9b007kvycXTb/cfbdAJ2XF7skI9WtpQdaT+fuR5UCGtoveEzvJ7RFBVZPUkz6jMPVDLBsU62GUUsBxHqDidSx8yRhXGujFqW5LvZL0JCtoq+b1Znk53lEqGvC/2xdrjBQo9w+ZqZtKfgAC9fO2Gt/VXxi+1dv89lf1QLS3tChH9oT9cIX5TpHw2aGNa0S++GNSYuYuNlukpJF63oWIRBS8oz7wHMpL5g0QyTUaKjdrIK6UE96oD21Wc33F9sn0Bjya7c1nxEb0+9XnqheRvjejc52VJx01zy4lHwMuYTRQQ5iB3/q1qkqDgugXr0Z1hBjy/whpyssCv+WYYYJElJ8vFHKY2V926cxgDnF06O0/QxQOtOahzvWL5JqS39lgUM+m0/DfzC3IrOg6QhmU1PLzsxa8aTEZMTr+HlQpReq/rgsXM5F7c34bsWlkJZ5rlDf5mI+yjp2wnyc9RL87UC9HTWQmcOFT0tb4p5TUA2Rn0AVLFU0aJoACgUVb3YFHenWhn1PAq8uonPfTCeN2guY9WPCaqcPrwnvxOvkhU1klm/VWNjuobfn4/jxvaSoguCAmtVwAjJKiIvQNV+NK/f77xKvKYcTBhSWzIT3pv8kiQQ5n9fRLEVxekLvCQ65k78J6NGEYob0BzSD4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17017","langCode":"vi","question":"zt9xT2l06pz4uTgxeSb1awW05rYAzPaF41kSPtI3cfWm0diTLtOhuUZ+XMU+fxEt","answers":["been repaired","repaired","be repaired","repairs"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4Y8JBhc467FgQdSOkyqMmxWjo281xGHhWjU1gUJG67AvWb5YVDYJri/84pPICmzGavIQHgiGQ2NLhVmU2jwIjLwquxyGCNvffjRokd4HcUKsTV7rrBJFzy9iQteDxqCyvdQLK909u8cVjWdPatsOBCzt9my5WSTatrmIU3GL/jlrDWstlhireg0Feh/Wz5OqEIoPW8ZcO8oc4DErCfGrmaTharRsYmyXmgwyZ3tR1lq3VmfZJNXFpKCvTBElogKDxa5knLAVNiOkV1+BcbyDd5eTdZvMqmwEC03FbNsXYmF45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/M2bgE+hIJyh31kIPfcSV8sW5NRJgKlTZHfyzrFBjATmCZs3njJ+c2HdAop+JobSB+vOX25/KXmgppgd/yI+W8a6HCaHc7QNApWXbaT0YTBB"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17018","langCode":"vi","question":"tyrNoKOZv8pwgvjRyB+lju25/ajMbr4obR7wghypnRiS1ST/TvHZwRh4CshN7/DH","answers":["broke","broken","been broken","be broken"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5dXPlgORjbctTjcdHBkjS/oHJ/4XxKBXQojrIBCqHkFn1dbMa8O3Dae4iKbUotsibytnA0TabHAj0oySDnCro8UzpQMIHXRQAKhJEzi7auR7XMcYfDBrxLLmOC/P46NgCbWHA+20fLoNRN9cU2BJKMGD0z3iqRbrqfWHoECBks2lnddYsyebfz2thpgavGh1z7bk36z/V33y7ASIOIwjcozoLFTQAdno44FP/OZKfYhnmtMGduwKvmt7FgXvc8FAYD5gAKUc4OuPdqFKotAWf35dUTo/iIk6JwwQuEuaMgupjHXof1Ov58yO4W7pKhJDt1Zn2STVxaSgr0wRJaICg8WuZJywFTYjpFdfgXG8g3eXk3WbzKpsBAtNxWzbF2JheOcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPwqQe/j6jkb0NYQpTobFco3cYKMQAMS+FbIBuwwI9bigNfKOHgweQfpM+HTqxndwYzYTyhoqnBilS3UouDpmg42o55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17019","langCode":"vi","question":"sxwmti9eGzhhdMfiBXiNKr53Lb+xesvdjlBmN1ChOowP/YbSVUm9AYv5qrIoyYHqhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["steal","stolen","stole","to steal"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyibEKSleHEgPG+4YJKp837oHJ/4XxKBXQojrIBCqHkFn1dbMa8O3Dae4iKbUotsibytnA0TabHAj0oySDnCro8UzpQMIHXRQAKhJEzi7auR7XMcYfDBrxLLmOC/P46NgCbWHA+20fLoNRN9cU2BJKMGD0z3iqRbrqfWHoECBks2lnddYsyebfz2thpgavGh1yNvIMGJP7JXV/9GWEx3F0aT2jjL4YSYXHYxc4UO92SZ/0/ck2n/9PIg/+c0W5v9BCGJo55osGN+AwwkpHwH+lBGec7ojAjtGw8z+GSwFY6jE1MkknQZwuRPrIbUOYoOMMgiFSDyuixy7Mh5SsGs/0POhfKwYOBRnDtqHx/DLcrx6LsvIuQZEWuvOEvuT1QabE9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsODeVjDsPED1WdXg0v85H5WqzJmfQfwKWIU9t2ufFfPcVaVoafHf4DaRU8KXFH0Tk5QEBS0L1cabqzm1giwejTXWABjizh9xpfmmJ+bsX0mS5g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17020","langCode":"vi","question":"Yj1xnVz1Qv7Jy4Q8eaaQWx99WD/634HmxWuJtcuWcEly0ZN8t4tEow8ADB53QkFG","answers":["been serviced","to be serviced","service","serviced"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE01Ww9ZCavNK8nZyN7kO/3dWjo281xGHhWjU1gUJG67AvWb5YVDYJri/84pPICmzGavIQHgiGQ2NLhVmU2jwIjLwquxyGCNvffjRokd4HcUKcxS2HYywDRzALk2AGUYU1XXYKWF0oM3p93YpIKISMWSukXZGP3anPs9w1SvVdbUFQLCv6p0Va9Hf+qMemU6n6Tvd53O6VPEiiZLMG4+ww2wJTR5rSvLQXQC6ufl2HijayCIVIPK6LHLsyHlKwaz/Q86F8rBg4FGcO2ofH8MtyvHouy8i5BkRa684S+5PVBpsT0CHyp5wd56B7ToOtcSw4B3RtgLNGvDvM5YAk0Vu8fNVn5XePkjWSHfAR+Y6kjSBWUmube+XJ3GBqgJbAL3RQa0KAyufXfULxaggilkRfK+RXFZvAZvpj1Q6EuvKfSwP"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17021","langCode":"vi","question":"X9DRaDZnhU/4aXTG5Celm/oCoLUMT3Uqunx8RMcyGc3cdmJQ1ypSrVuUhUIpZQKS","answers":["make","been make","made","be made"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzms2C8PzmuShdvn2MgNtGXNAQGAZgdv/BD1nPTxdlYYS31TfnMa41dvOhKnjdzWuyThIRto3uw+lIwSKwAA+WK6DPgLaMtVGfcxxwu0g6YYC65ctDDFdSoDw3oLFAp4T9nkKKsohGXvfIneloas4xoDVahE8/1vuBclc2fPA7NnLtukU9rALsaL0XTrhD3teu1vO1iOJHwGu9FeYLswGwsjc0nxV18k7dfSkHihEJJEVqDbxrep/Dc8Dhdx+YysDLSQxiyjBweTPOBwrlu37P8QqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjXjSSiB+OaCnJ3mnmbV7n2vcFYCiTb+A4dbrSqgVfjh9a2zhctpGi5MH3j4q8EdEsGMRUZRkEHzaHpHbJUNXdcg\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17022","langCode":"vi","question":"s5M5LOjK25YUu6ENL/LbVEKXn8k43meVfNdUXSE/VcgrafSga9m6UOlTkPjTo/dp","answers":["to be opened","open","opened","be opened"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/2X/eMIo7uMA9HNkpvoRbPBT6kIRUnepRfI4ZKwKTfe8CXX+J7EXVJU3s4V4BVNgO8/PaIp3RVBvUA0uV9uWeVk8X/ql388yH4KjPX7QBHnPHAZ4i/DrTIVYriiCd4r1Q0BORCHcbcDFu4+r2Y6h04zOYGdRW+e3fCTlns2ubqZh+dKL9FbMJsPeC3OWSG79/GZHcFW89PbcMfQKC3Ppx9blz8GuMoaFE7QCcH6RhfzYMN7W5Vgz0sg8j8foCH2m9gPyd6INd+3heRyEETh1MLccXqJC7WLfjmTmFwrs1WwExMMQCgbMQMgZJktX/1/hMv6WCYUFj7e9KnrgZta+0+zHmKGJc7EkJNFAr/PCzLXuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuLJ4k8TkUh2T18hPdXO7zsMIfmVumedgvlfJ7/FxHxQpIEQaUQR0LIjUB3+Ih4sOEPaL2SrL/I4OdZYKAvs1Eo0iivgGiLOcFY5lyF5YqidzQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17023","langCode":"vi","question":"kj3JoRKUsa9j7qeUMFZTlJc8XvJq1xXME3qCCbp6M7w\u003d","answers":["to be made","made","be made","make"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1M3Xsx6lv/SQGV59vl30ZofgqWjV9qWDkNVIhuSTG/8uAnWV95MzE2UsVNWf2NtcBCDUx6o0g1VMy5KWavOL7nyDmY0y/rlNZ4tWrbSZnuy3SVV2DsFeAsdNKAy8PsGCEt74iJf/HeaXDBf1j2Zrel2QZRCer6Ny9TWlGjWTGIIl/9oTBj0zOzJ6JO6+O+KeJxw8yTro6ODE6ytIBNKW8AU2HtnKWlJ8OboGTm/k0B+fayCKBISMUHcAxqtqOkcNkartUouwONRfFLv6Y+Oa4XhcQoxpe7qxrKZTsMazDkw+xty+l04e9sWYNjprjH68ZYGQRPs8h3iTEkDhAxssoIuR/2dJXkwBO1RnAf6m8aU8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEBMRZKxN9xv9lMAvSuib73VDjDIMMGHk96ffXlVHvFoiqB0ggXDusm7x2te7kJhVAc\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17024","langCode":"vi","question":"04RfG/F8NzkeISD4zF1/9QSA6Sl63EchIhlaxCBTalAWTI3DaTOqLNoeuiWplmkNWdnMrAMpzI9N/uegYWgQhA\u003d\u003d","answers":["to be turned off","be turned off","turns off","turned off"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+hI3Khuyz2oz3toxreZKOCVDUZd+MqjB8/Lgjti4oSEKYl21XlOryEkT4HAjDDFBSeyOPf0le0OuFbNE2I/bZWi9fczCXGu8pDUon3Twdn1gstb6sI07TC8/4VTdQUqP7YNetHlNTOpSMU+Y+yeB89P+ii5MolhuApTbQZbRFfRhnJkqc/Xbo5LGYKX0VGvZnhvuiMAp5eJKrUOx3h5M0+jXi3+FXA6+UrOi8Rzk+gycj0e6a+UKA6+KsAd2xhtuiUq27HDcGCDcEWgFFvzhd3ocY+tsx1jWUK1XRdhQ02qJwvX5gMjAY3GdM1Nb8X1IBO1tRzOCoTCzI8wXFQC9PNCnMwJjPhqemZ9jFHXYkFQh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8W4XsySCLV1I5QjoJrTVpUxDfC9JnusKEVwQ/3m/cTSiR2qbZ5IGFOd+fkrS392JjonKHgWzlBqGvQQpSNlrKqwf2v6vKWDnEy+mUgdmVGN3dhJXftmX9AmIEbJqp8G9sw\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17025","langCode":"vi","question":"EMjUpeOPUaGUdIYf7fA4HxlAGtigiNo6WuqjvEDyRSLJOSsGODRShyTHaYo+Srbw","answers":["be left","leave","to leave","left"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEy9rVkfac2onT+/RaVqjG+8MVr70fG/FxCBCH44nUm2ug9jMnZFqNQwO3ukOMVxYia/UfAv8UBZi13f19euM+mMYlq+EOLxDk7w4Ljkbi7tK3qE3drxpzSEGRZWJacAahEIFb7m9RFKShlvXDVuKRzCG0H6c1fZpS9IIBRRrH9RHw9sY4YXPfMfF7eePlHoEP/+Kplvc/k1oy6EJHrVLzckgJ87+eXy0MD02N8OBAF0xZD2a788j/an+pJubWIeU9uslHrW1DciI+Lcafi/wHh5S3Rh5G4hkDiHRpMhyGdhFCDB2Rodfr8Y2nugO3GqiXPpS++Z4xPeKRw/J/8bhl9h2hmb/38wptAPU6j2q6/VHlgTLWfDmOsKuNK/NgjKN6B5Q7f3Tie1ubikwn609Sctm/0xzxQmgfIC+UD0AQaKNrj10TYHfGvmxsnM5JVMhQEd2fekXdLxuajB19np86a3GcLDivrquGeKEqggtedIvpIsPlGslxjPL98wmARYp3t3dNJpVcOtO7r/s+1j1oqj/Ga3UigiWDV7U9R6F/qRk2weIAygQHC9+ym7S7sdbH2+tW+W8BcjG3OYx/PChVFVgCEwn/Jr3YCa3vu/OzV/uHUDUmvpxq5ix/7ODH9uyqc9VR1AGRjRCJhrQsgvAYrEvoGUQUvOnhua2lyBkrXFX9/RvNweXBsCsyFSpBdjOAGBJv0hCkAPgkyTsI6+1xSkszr77gC4P9DwYvZ+nl4qFFB2B3B0Q5SRE/rTwyrxXXEfTVqinkQuTwv4sk6z6kZQEcTp6gVe1hv1yTwTqKvaT2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb483ODg2Q1tXERwWKTTYmd0U6rFS776Z+ZldJ0k+q8Da5ABDZ7DcZHD8miLn9o9Y58I+1VUkXbTFs+f2yZ59Tth4oeHcMA6bhj7+9ufR2z6a"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17026","langCode":"vi","question":"IQas26QB8S/Oaa0e5bcLgYfdqgDwsgwSTh/I1XDcmfY\u003d","answers":["to ruin","ruin","to be ruined","ruined"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2aQrNdNkOk5gCLPG08+cb2/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE9LxyUamb+IhbDyg+AXITaas4OpCwWydXwSQB1UVWfT+nYqgiPd/lbesj1HD06gvJ3v70mUTChWQSNhIKs1Fwo9b/zPzzPZQioqElyEOpFDJWTIJCefQVdlkrx4puh+cPfjGWM2prmrM9QAPldoRMQrSoSADVT2iDYESNdqgZ86VJCUVeWfX9mNpvikJhSCjnKlKv6kkLi0sD+lJjfwK8tNjAcFq+jcYZX/mj6pnh9SmEcsPWioghWkjX7He0fMHvMT7666EA4UjkIbq0PR6xOBclQHgeZ6xqB2KHBkoQ2wMbo21l4+SimbaLyBtGRrdb+6fktfWRJzoZD4S6HsZcwtWrmsLdR8lykljHvacy2LeEvyKWQG1a6g7cUB+GqcHkEvSwpcBUDdKhw6dypaZV6ouJbrYE9zT9zgSPxY/ytNt2M5yOmN8rjcN5JIGUw4o3wifwofPwl6TxgLGArznVdGR3pxBCR1ufa1i/ONJW1LEI6EwW5wxXXFub0hcEyCAzzYPFx0ng8maYmwXiMr0E8+s9VR1AGRjRCJhrQsgvAYrEvoGUQUvOnhua2lyBkrXFX9/RvNweXBsCsyFSpBdjOAF7SoCB2P/UhPrMUgLsNahwby1xLAhVHMXLncKAY2kHDONGe0YR1iVcLm4WW3pSk6YmglqeU2IYRN37CI67IITW8EDJ4oKobA24BU0GQBRBVBPYyHupw+2toYKueAtjQvZJb10odibTKyqHnPuj7RGO1E+2EzZILCxyBidAJQRBrTa9rKO10WDwDde8HuHPDIkF6QI/7VkQrWCaqcJ+5Od00sGsIjbEi9nvC5jAyxfT5sEUhBYJ8lhaQDl4sP2j3QM1jgqFR1kujmMCpRcZRW2BGXmhJxNmuRg8L9y1dAevo8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFECFx/PRFSfb37mhk6ZQ3cUxSvw0Z772rhEtcXZf0E30QclVzJEdauF11iMe+GoDM4Y\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17027","langCode":"vi","question":"KEz6KR2DnFRmsSPwhJ+9diJ4cIJJj7DhiDog4KK2odeBEDJCt263DwRwwGa4o6Bkh7pBGoBnMBjiO+qK0JA/sYRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["play","to be played","played","playing"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwoOPG0vSlvr6ZRNuEBszUu/y9XEZ24vn7wSkmnQBUE9LxyUamb+IhbDyg+AXITaas4OpCwWydXwSQB1UVWfT+kRq4p4pBYRqUF1LbUSiZsSjow/KykOsL86c+9g7m1BhGi8Gcpo9qlOiAYTK6m2Mz6yRzLjgttzkbkH19Sy8V0WIBK6C7FCymx8Mry/iTDLQRKY6LdRtZeMjJVOpkstBqrny7e5XqTLGvHCJYq/T/Bi1xcj+BS5vaolDoOgCo8g1fZo/BhRLToQHpUN9iu/yZzV7nMBPXvqUqXGFhuYLre+cH/j7Y7ELCnW8bnWkgc0CftD1+BBgF3u0V66EpryJKDXBcnvViqow+8UKdO/w7nphXO5j8GVnT8mfFGaOQQ7P+EJJZCvU/mrfORDc/wJZrF16Kk8/FpNt55UOT8ou3zHzbWzxFpBIbIp+3+dZ3Xiikt9U35zGuNXbzoSp43c1rt7OXAgYcPZYYa0W0jnhmXoCOxS2qG4vCmPp64t5g7A1hgIV00WffF7DpD2xUBxDZjM3eghml0ZvFZERXEnRcY2/ViBNL7q2MAebcAXUjc4Ds9VR1AGRjRCJhrQsgvAYrEvoGUQUvOnhua2lyBkrXFX9/RvNweXBsCsyFSpBdjOAF7SoCB2P/UhPrMUgLsNahwby1xLAhVHMXLncKAY2kHDONGe0YR1iVcLm4WW3pSk6YmglqeU2IYRN37CI67IITW8EDJ4oKobA24BU0GQBRBVBPYyHupw+2toYKueAtjQvZJb10odibTKyqHnPuj7RGO1E+2EzZILCxyBidAJQRBrTa9rKO10WDwDde8HuHPDIkF6QI/7VkQrWCaqcJ+5Od00sGsIjbEi9nvC5jAyxfT5sEUhBYJ8lhaQDl4sP2j3QM1jgqFR1kujmMCpRcZRW2BGXmhJxNmuRg8L9y1dAevo8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEA9rDN044w1KVarZuhudltmRBIuZLdQ6hM+VdQfT3D6zbtWtTy92fh0i8RybzXNdmcJwsAIjYT3XNXsaJgs/SPOJec2ZftOmvqUEksXou68NMB48VyP8P0JjrR1UZXse2s\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17028","langCode":"vi","question":"MPiCMQZrUN5nRKdO7vEqMT0SqTkXuOdN57EvjoeBLha+AJaYqT2gXrkJdK2XbMrDTATx3ARF1ZCqKpCbhhDVP31U5Hjcx+3+nyLqR80XgRU\u003d","answers":["come up","to be come up","coming up","came"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0PDKAyq4hDKlRyAeHZyahUZ8tAUbWlGBvwxNsiVEue7S+fLENx4R0YdzPqXP5A+VxLR8Ha4Ffl6/XPFUbGzEBBT2eaybU5WO5b7jYH4dTL5dZ2x43BftPPU2KZhQhUSWUIFb7m9RFKShlvXDVuKRzCG0H6c1fZpS9IIBRRrH9RHw9sY4YXPfMfF7eePlHoEP/+Kplvc/k1oy6EJHrVLzckgJ87+eXy0MD02N8OBAF0xZD2a788j/an+pJubWIeU9uslHrW1DciI+Lcafi/wHh5S3Rh5G4hkDiHRpMhyGdhFCDB2Rodfr8Y2nugO3GqiXPpS++Z4xPeKRw/J/8bhl9h2hmb/38wptAPU6j2q6/VHlgTLWfDmOsKuNK/NgjKN6HfCoIoV7GTvgRNGDS7W+DGbi6Xm75CsKWPX4gfDWMrrs9Wx0q9PHoV06rzt91EzwL/zPzzPZQioqElyEOpFDJWTIJCefQVdlkrx4puh+cPfjGWM2prmrM9QAPldoRMQrSoSADVT2iDYESNdqgZ86VJCUVeWfX9mNpvikJhSCjnKlKv6kkLi0sD+lJjfwK8tNrIezWmHS71UjylNeuyBWWCyI9cUSSpdiXjkkKRcuZR2gsVY1ByhgvCoP0dJTyggDKA8/Ax4GYnxG6LSxGbYNaRLT+TY8CQ4IebeyUfQJ3gflQVdfQBJr1ehvWJHVgB/tZMF4PQwohtA5u8hV1TFZrbVGafaK9ntVTMWkXRDRiz6xMrUT8P/VJxNGtfGZa2RTwFLw0xpcywhy20qlVxs5CxHdn3pF3S8bmowdfZ6fOmtxnCw4r66rhnihKoILXnSL6SLD5RrJcYzy/fMJgEWKd6Cy4zXr5/Bao/jLC9PE/++iaCWp5TYhhE3fsIjrsghNYTlYJUWooEyw0PyUoZ8/iPAlg1n45CZTg73pDB9hoIxzPzJwdcS4YM68WVGuH7MnSXXVY8Hem7Ca2jycAEPGvmv/iLTu7HDfWfvnRGopn2vf9rfZSaC5pHFJGk6g2xDxdT8riNITwM+5he9PhBft3SXEUPJeYQA/F++FKL8DEusb3YFHenWhn1PAq8uonPfTCeN2guY9WPCaqcPrwnvxOsaHbroTddLzqYH0sfEIXGbUh76M6+UKOeE8vsQ80ibrxZBkiivLQluUs7bX2CcJjLCCYAFadh6o7wC3CGqh6PW8siJrFrOlIXBxhUTkaGcKuCGbDnWt4cHfJ8dzJ+t9cPHwcf0basTAVmYHL2wMApazIiw/bE0EiFQO81b5YsOeg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17029","langCode":"vi","question":"IRfRepcup963fz5lRcMzhBPkJz4VpvPLUpgryUNeJOhUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["to hang out","be hung out","hang out","been hung out"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+rKyhxboRS85h/yqZbB5Sw2g5XHzzWev7rKvqv3CDD9leiWFIvLZhfS9E6wGtpgbyT7haxgUTIC4EaW2pp2tQShjp/SnfEwrHR+cKDayfph215DS/aBkBeQGK/Ry4WGq1ah4k3jFa1coB+GKdVcpmxi1I/lbYfMu3Sy9Fwo5qw3539X4c8rPE3OwhnXTc296C6yDMXEFPjQjhbj1NBcWRfPFpjNwddJx5kNQEPrrYqG99syv+1226cyJGXK5/XGKuOvZUFRFvIOXs9yEO1YDn/eJF0T8apl5EaWSLh3MoFr9cKVNX/WEh2StyrnAyiI/If4b+Ngcsc1ki2x0YuRK+kf2sHGk0HlrIoSgqqiZXvF7CB90d+GWixVlKhZ2VglAbnAnP2bUC6Yva87bsOg8DwOloNYFFNLzNds1Y8l0RJGtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17030","langCode":"vi","question":"xk0FhJsQn4qJTuExCakMZyTHhrmLxwqXcNqd2Khe7v3331ARQayqA/t4xi9WOPgT","answers":["to me","me","of me","Ø"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEz86Opr0XFb0sp/LSRwdWSnoCakykRhx2BqQyumPdnOnRBPNLOZhKIzfWn6YTkIygptH4T72F4k5fvomnQ4u3FT2QDhKAdVPNxlo0B+ssqN98V40/PPvR/ZNnFmYj0EGH0eGlsvuA8N8eQZgCDHLGBWlW0Qhb34U7sBhvEeLifDXoWrTyZNpRxHoRtT0yVJw6TpUtpMXP/DEoLpCIbwYmm0IQw6eSo+sTorjfzkOfNoDSW9dJBuVFAad+JYjmMHp9H41mbySzPm+kBXwGObTP0WNnQ55vuSYcBFmum3jpcjFCC/XmWq1bIxH9v4o/HRv174T5QnFi6eCHeEdudhtGxzin4bSpjwNlRBFbbR6HmvM8DMkhQtFNSQ52fXhG4qA1ROUfnsf9+yy61shn5aCkJTqPL+BHZSvHvesnCc/9o44Z64o/GNCIWoq82rTjO+DXbtxJcYx5iTFY52NQvq/75O5gmtR6rGEbrXPiAk6wx7j6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4lBN0HBxWjPS4OOe4H3wmB/zNQfDEOhLUcqY+5UDXE4heRN8bnjwKNaGskK5RUKitc6JPqiHEp8tWjD41Uh6ThX"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17031","langCode":"vi","question":"MhaJxImquTfNTzUehvaps8t+Bg/fbwALPrjzPZEKFKqwWp2moWPayBQSgVfeJ5DH","answers":["of me","Ø","for me","me"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3SntybM+7TBrJIPbTyM4M6zO52RVUu4k6oG2EsFDAw6n1dbMa8O3Dae4iKbUotsiXdmMECwv/ZhY1+SKXpYZ97qedNdjHXlvUbehgI+woT3WFeWwRsfTErNqjJmkqACt4Gq22nkWjaJbXCqeEeLw0i9Vq5JUCdLPedKKhwb+Ctq7L4dzPiPm1shvylWehrfNTj8SgW0yCFRgnMenkjmw2j+XB9eIs/IXdc8Qz3JeDt6a6x+tX4Em0aSesB3vxM/GaiFmJrlF5Gz54JdAq743F69X12Pmj4vGtqVkBbz7FLM39hzpQWq8yS83I2NN6UnSudls8GxOOrQ7UOOEX+1ajx1I0oLdFIp8XF3nsYmr7ds54lZO/8CS/Fbs8TD0i4Puby4FoWpEESrR6thxakUb7/5WLbPScdZcbDFGJi8N4g2kwIZHp1P+7gJjAW/yeDufbWump012OhT4EySELt768Y45l1V4Ac5jJsSrg081nyQuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuIZSdTfBZLTn2JKOs+Q/nxgcZbO/AN+ZjjlUmu3658wKTp8RNr+BtaBoi+gKIBA6OAvy6IiNO1q+Y2cuyuhsRVM"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17032","langCode":"vi","question":"rsudWs317iaswpXokzK24zCqv7+We5TB1ytnn8qqUZo\u003d","answers":["treated","be treated","treat","to be treated"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzih7s4LAybGaNVc6qFPet4GBihSsIYpQVUJr7FTQbl3NatgvF9zrAV7VtQ5nq7WZsqJUVyQi02OYij0xyqGLY0UWszZn5boa0Q5MQREvRx6rGgE2sLqDfy/4nLAL/DzBCOGx9zXVLdKEBHc4yUQjFMGr7Ld2Rjj07I6knCgKl+FNz9qiBJAw7RL7bzLKLFqaCqDJqolmmKNOol1471+c8yvSpuuieuBDEMDW50QP7Sym3Z+2Wjca7HL3QoKTvC7MfMOUrsy5UuClQZPHwckHI7WbKc5rtvGwkhk2RRN3CqoAEoSFwi1DlDJtMr1MQEycdkpmq9PgDYNy4qQ0W/lT3ADWpngMpZ7VuORkOwSMGk9thu5XoWBVPBgdzt37W8xvMuPlycrFO6yMK7yOOIcy0JBUaUZ4sll75AMC14R7i5kFxpjDfqQC9avuMoy3dWiDxtcAT2h/z9+FPlguGJCtnuKxCXkX08kx362+9BteVxh6pBSsbuWI1Hhrjbh1Dhtc3gBu2Ve61YOec2e+PKsAdqnPR2ZHHToKBzWNAMYASNW0q1Hr4uQB+G3gbil1Yi/PshcnuBIVug7EoMOaWEzo0c/imy9ZfH0IM1rUsKvaM7KLurfwkQkAfqkJa70Rze+iqH1vFz7aE0Ky1Xdap5welg\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17033","langCode":"vi","question":"fcB5HpP89n36vE1FaBLcC+Z9KQbAzjqDdonCA3H/OWCpvvWI4AnLTQkN+GnGGBLl","answers":["employ","should employ","should be employed","be employed"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE55F8uFeqDQuiElJm1v/z7bKJ4qrlOrv67LBknqePOl/sGMFIqU5Xo5uZmV4qjnmwyhxurvw1LEaP3S5kfL0P67FOEaVyL/6vHYgKg+UXiHux0Aef4ymwYn8qrj2NDvHQeLew/R4giYfr0ubLdoZwL19s0UNQDTJ65lu/6AQTnXfhJ4XfXi2lPEPDcyb851Z9+SVejgbHpaUiXNH+YkR03+JoJanlNiGETd+wiOuyCE1GG6k2tPJkl2D49H/Lk9tE62QzZSLOb2/KMVfkWfPqYY3cM+Hie1JFPpTCzhjTZSNc/a3XWV6+k4a2uEz/s4i2ZID0B4uPPuD8016YKQpLLph4TUtT+x3A67if8/I2MBCmvt7Mwz5TrV7i+5F5MQw1iHv+HXJf9Hc088AHQ3KNzMG+lW/ZfTKrPS7etjLCZVvMc60EYEQgnmZrvi7mDaqhWjZLjCq2Y5bWutsbHcYKk9UgbmOPmg8lowwNsG0JuDx6BhVsKCvEQgIYMcJ0PE2gqDU5UxcDMHWcjBtOmmlPuCnPR2ZHHToKBzWNAMYASNW0q1Hr4uQB+G3gbil1Yi/Pn5nbR43GgoE80F+ylNnecPoqYd30tlBBjH5qbmoT7Y6Svz10H61pXY0c9toSZjV9qxjExdsrqnaYBgDhb77+1o6efmYoHgF+C0RVLCnRD4A"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17034","langCode":"vi","question":"TatA5KhzJCErVGM8e8OGm1SRW/OENvLTDPKF2tDA/eo/b5N0nHX2lxeFwuc7Iy6WAZLU6Jj/BPaGvrPIbAApJw\u003d\u003d","answers":["be consumed","should consume","should be consumed","consume"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE55F8uFeqDQuiElJm1v/z7ayf4A0HaWcuFHFgqEEGncZsGMFIqU5Xo5uZmV4qjnmwyhxurvw1LEaP3S5kfL0P67FOEaVyL/6vHYgKg+UXiHux0Aef4ymwYn8qrj2NDvHQeLew/R4giYfr0ubLdoZwL3YCGtrHQA5oPfvK5HG2Ji+oWj9zLYlDMSNqNvgMU3b1hfIBKDtJiEqjbRLnj3sSXxJE40/pNHSF0cdLNET7nL+KcZ/oLrGfbD32byaoC4pPQ1Vg6yXottXKVKESIiGi7PVkDF296cTF9cUzGg/ySUqiVPZ3FtvmVByNoySBR6AHFsG8yvfnkI45kkypnGeumR42px4zdOwTYULVpNg9aqI/GnX/DtkrRMbmtLh0L4kHInA4p4LBIza3eTfKQIT50r6aVkxOXgRfs74NuHu5eSqE7LRTcT2ovLPmz9oQEmh1/t4kpBZgR++i47gT3tDJL2bS7dCqSgvtoQfgUWUdh24LM6++4AuD/Q8GL2fp5eKhcU1mdgC18PaUqN2/9eipSrAXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8d4SoBZrrGLEwEEbeI4AXIQDFnW30tnSP/+GDLrPeTP1FI0+bHmftmjhgsy12OPfqNQuUMTh8jjlWqFIgg/WrZ2l41AwnJ6ab93VIFDqlJ4iHihLFU5+IeFCwSR2js7PtoRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17035","langCode":"vi","question":"b5FMITpE0T3BlGV91F54UnTIX8GQbgFJkluZKDQMTLVtzIgQ8pxPBHI+mbWGlicFcskO8kN2uwngtYg2onpCAw\u003d\u003d","answers":["should be sold","sell","should sell","be sold"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE55F8uFeqDQuiElJm1v/z7bgLj5v6YwCWEU37T0f2kERAlx6DgIsht5q1F74byIyYoV0B7dyHDHEjANk2Eyii9VqbaX50sFZodQ0FwDhdmF2PKY3V7iqx6xyJlVtKcA6dtBnkVe2JoL+lLjGT5jbT1QMlBJA8Ii6KK4DejtezPUaLT8COmC17c2JCzfB1qXNkP9xHHNhTHYhmSdhVf+X5I1RnoSPpZ7WhsKMxh4KaeVePRizHq8Z8DnUbqa0Fab+ULud/dk2ELkvKZFrLNobFLHBKi4R+24Q6yimyTga0DSUfJlq2NAWYRT0dRVZRoZMxfXunWkWiZY0cNz/BdnOeVsJN1D3Dc73VbaIcTd+q4l7bhvL1tPBYGe4CBItrJnjE3tW0jAYfuQBh3S6YcLdhLjfzd3Med6WXl0A4Y3X9C/4bbUTWX8Ka0qaZ9kyZY/P6EpUmdolUlJim3PNzNK36WpFdDAjWMHfuQ8NhsPq3HlYaLwZymj2qU6IBhMrqbYzPhnPsrXbixFhpDhYRLkAObTYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdv0F9eshkEIlSPe5hy8xrcEmswuewnuUcnkT5R1C3H3ZjiS0avUrI170iwWKY6p7DC2CXwlsP8sXInD4HwkzQuhOgsVkdEPk6cEqXTVAIbnsf7ALRhrI0fglas8b3FANDcy8t5pxzD2lupWeFXv/x5sA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17036","langCode":"vi","question":"8t8RHVywU3FdgxtfcRY3K5Xq5bRoch/Ye2pdEVF7bm1c5fgtFDKdgYHolB9ih6k/","answers":["be given","to give","give","to be given"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExfG5PB3Fk3WwwMdG0toYB/z9ExWU8CkrLVkh7tDD51duc2L7Z27oxrhSkTNyP3ZZdIAkd5WIoe0t/OqSYXGMhhMnaLTodjXhBBuIS+VnivfJZcoG8UjD1ACWEetL6y6FKLKiVI885qBx7aQ9p1deZj15t2RHmucwv07WqQ4EdwMerP1IfelOjEbUXYIrlb5uuEhDFKzJgzzF6bwDvsyibO9eX63vBrDy7hNeVozFkYzzW816XJ2XU/mVqTB+kZIpOyWRxby0LnfBgedR0OWKAPyqPUal77aeRG95lGoc3Hk2Li4ESh9xAjovtLS2KPRpBctDvrtBAiqAAhrtu7RcjrJRmx7M/P2qwGHq8FqUv9ecHzFpzjh/csA2nnmlMCsUM8WGAemEVzXQ6ZqFqmk8Dn6CVanfN5RyJaT3H8XFVDa088CFvFydfFeBR9/jyV/hyDIZUX0SL+tzyVbzDcDVk4\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17037","langCode":"vi","question":"1wPPA1nZlgZxxGQCOqjf5vJh6ky3yT+rIXnRNoBQ/9njrG2LRBbGV5Zmf4t5fmDT","answers":["be invited","invited","been invited","invite"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2u9ldxumKbwZpuRjVa/+Nj9Be4gBIa8xKt4enVfmWv3v/M/PM9lCKioSXIQ6kUMlYDGMKNl7HaFkAdBixnrenryHXdsn9qdoAyYwffZUf52r+gxKQrgA/P4P5v5Lqhyl9Tteu+d2ZHRwoTAaMLA411ni1a6h2NvM6qvq+uZyFu+RHqdfSufP3lVHsassseRxi0yUyYJkTrt+DUBrTpHviroJfuAAcMSxDELJdvrTTtIdTUgaHhSXT5qbA+eRJwwvocenjj/tv5c/gvir+vkGUQANP/BbIoGWMj/CT62apu4PEYB231IVnGrsQjjjnS9G6c9HZkcdOgoHNY0AxgBI1bSrUevi5AH4beBuKXViL8+/wCSIW/VgroVgcZ85dV9SScYPpa3F8GLYNxqv3f6b83+EJxoVPnPGzJInBnKlDH5LhhJRvOwPHnT78+8WWQAeQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17038","langCode":"vi","question":"V+mEKuxBSw++svZEcP9LHvkkDnT0ZTA77fmJ6122UZ8F1LpmS4xkUKZ2SnLmgVNs+/DKBgMBWM5s8kd1Fbvn4A\u003d\u003d","answers":["to be made","to made","made","to make"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0RI8kOFdFtF4FeOjvvILCrIRJkO2yxx0PIMdkFvl4kxUZ6Ej6We1obCjMYeCmnlXsin9ohEYku6XywXQl+Tl8V961br3EQZ/25+I3CsPlZk+5pEcPCbCm9khOgbusFOTPWYm/egyLdaoa1NGHRZQlLWJVkPgIFhO6lKPGhwttKT4b3t+ta2OYYllzyEAxnSxiNzSfFXXyTt19KQeKEQkkTmCAyYS11/SyxcojX0u6dECxsx/B6gmETr169gmQlAbxf/1dSP85/rcEhIZt0CsD/QrW46A5uJXdKTbGrHmKqXo94/m3jxd9zPm3WenKLqk2xujFl7COWpf9FJPAtWzPXYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdvvIZJ3HcsSAeK3xfANkPVbHesBOVRRIalDSvLbzyDd9uk4QUX9B3T0cRlJoh8Mtvbzq0x5pThRbmKYzRQYSsgMVp+kfuq3hoLAxC6wOK/9+ctapHBaV3QC/dUbsax3VLp2phBYatAOUvD1btgjIxAZw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17039","langCode":"vi","question":"+Gj6a9Haw5+Kg7J5UM2SU3X1klNxo471uWYsVWlrqK1rCllbe3gMkFywYgRhIFjPAByvQEv9koJeVE+tQM6xBA\u003d\u003d","answers":["attended","be attended","attend","to attend"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9J9Y+Rb6xQng1zKxEDwGCZUnv4vq3TrJ5bdibRBj9SaaLwZymj2qU6IBhMrqbYzPipg0LtwEp8Ojb7/4zQZwKdEewbmxZM/BxCfCAfZWJrJlRxTDIPSapAIuCe7PzuwDTHrspGu5xnzgW+7Imium3OTNzgJb/fjmmT4xFxoinkHG8vxGT2/DtoiLWOykbyxrRklZrAzvC/Etjz08MnW9GPYrs0qjS+SDA0uAgxstL+TCBOqeV65P/kG1m2AqCLcqkzjMLVBeS4qZv5AABhj7VOCFIxNe+Y1Mev4EIhnMzYnEjOpM0yqGNlwI2oxtMtseelI11iOjloEFsBSme9eVBFQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASap6zo8fAh1ZKHqh4g41ucwDpkSvYAEsLVZte91lwjBWI2U0+5WIhmwYeirVlyKHOosvgC17Cl2YypNHgOUY697qEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17040","langCode":"vi","question":"/1pJnXOqwOUvsNz2l7Ad8EzHVFBZN6hN+c+GJ+tVoM+Tgn7eGHe2phtbWltUoBYF","answers":["for","with","of","to"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9OMWlwovbuMpW7dYAHGJZLNAQGAZgdv/BD1nPTxdlYYRqu1Si7A41F8Uu/pj45rhdBa4DvsDVIAlxv86F9/DJm0/kqanmFT9UxCpbbYrt0rvxILZufDZqlc78VoYn95GCTYanvJ/IaUfrIklzD7SfoyZeKA7G0AqYiF1fU79wiBL4AslFnM7ytb8bAwclJX+7cXjnb+baKdk3ryLX/TBouHh+pYBMR78m9rFAgJ+9KJKyhfda4tQhY5bt55QZNZPzZyMRuCjWpVY8IZT2SxNYzy42dsuuKZrJn3krU0bhdZXdfLk5Ht181eTeJXNZ8UQAYLac6PCXniQpTiXW6mwq83XNHNe87AHv72yGx4Pd6oY5KJE6NY3c5gfeq9VNZGdFw6mtMdJjjPkxiI5PqL9Rg\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17041","langCode":"vi","question":"OHdRnRBNpTK4jS49VLgzAB8cdhKYdbmLDI31z6ZUkHyisP8zgvu8nDlh3QP8AcTo","answers":["of","with","to","for"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9OMWlwovbuMpW7dYAHGJZLNAQGAZgdv/BD1nPTxdlYYRqu1Si7A41F8Uu/pj45rhdBa4DvsDVIAlxv86F9/DJm0/kqanmFT9UxCpbbYrt0rvxILZufDZqlc78VoYn95GCTYanvJ/IaUfrIklzD7Sfo9m/cZeB6Dw5KmpFCwAe5CJtYcD7bR8ug1E31xTYEko7ii2JTmmmAUJgBCj/ZaTePMJ5s0gy/SSSY52qUi4Hqluv3B7hC4OCaBzrP/QTj8N5r8O3am8nfe0Np4UmmWvvDAXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8TfsS6Y4uIO7Va5jJE54aU8CFsXW07/J6tYvQ2s1yfitY3w7GaIRtJ+HjIKPCt55NK8qig7fGWYFORSa85wiMJ0\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17042","langCode":"vi","question":"vRxuu2p8R1gOVOjHehpWPe0UIaE+WiER0pL64WFJPmedVC179z+A9mNeZw1baE6r","answers":["to wait","waiting","wait","waited"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3O6iMwZ4QYgV++ZHr0pYoXIRJkO2yxx0PIMdkFvl4kxUZ6Ej6We1obCjMYeCmnlXlH+mLsRnE8WfamUfPgG+DFFJAKfHSAgbA+SQh6Hzl+/HrqcyKvAzKf3lCoZNXJJv9wmwOgr75YkDy/6tAcpoDRmnTO0ysdITjhR29N8SqcqwzznjFtHRdLxer1HpmkNYlxEEns3rmI5BT0KiirtCR6QQd6vdTlthFbVZzdb7HbRLy+4I/tf2rG3LaSxfSpvn1/Ms91lmOrB2pYkK+fL5bgmchd04V22aw/hMBxs9Wa5aduDPggrLXzqOWE5uAnm3Rau0yvhFLf/8CxDM8S5nI7aocA5onvRihsWj0r9Ex9jAWxXdXqugkAcoD3Nxj+lqYD5gAKUc4OuPdqFKotAWf36xcYvbsLnIRfLuROQRZJmuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuITxtN00ulCixf66pCvQf/7DV3w2+a6ClyianHdjuGJOzomnEU9mORL7R6oYT/NMefq+zjvaOSuQ+l/yt8mV+EOhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17043","langCode":"vi","question":"UNcI/i81ClSo1wXC6xuv3icH/2c4LBbCxKbkCBCgE1z6FJ1MV0yU0pqtkTbTl865nhi1bhoFse+ixRea7it50g\u003d\u003d","answers":["played","play","to play","playing"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwoOPG0vSlvr6ZRNuEBszUvIRJkO2yxx0PIMdkFvl4kxUZ6Ej6We1obCjMYeCmnlXlH+mLsRnE8WfamUfPgG+DFFJAKfHSAgbA+SQh6Hzl+/HrqcyKvAzKf3lCoZNXJJv9wmwOgr75YkDy/6tAcpoDRmnTO0ysdITjhR29N8SqcqwzznjFtHRdLxer1HpmkNYlxEEns3rmI5BT0KiirtCR6QQd6vdTlthFbVZzdb7HbRLy+4I/tf2rG3LaSxfSpvn1/Ms91lmOrB2pYkK+fL5bgmchd04V22aw/hMBxs9Wa5aduDPggrLXzqOWE5uAnm3Rau0yvhFLf/8CxDM8S5nI7aocA5onvRihsWj0r9Ex9jPlCr3Cw1XXCG9GOGgTB6QYD5gAKUc4OuPdqFKotAWf1J8m5Gac4VUhDfij2XMK4TuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuJT9Vb97jCeNxbx+mN2nSmxYvCZLBzlPUqvoIG87FNh+K+D5MNrVg/yP5SZvt3rBd+/HFDXoMS7DbxbofOTbbLgcQlZzr6zrYbGklDBsHnrLBoBJZR6BMJ/Lg7GNphwvTw\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17044","langCode":"vi","question":"mThoeToiYjYHDFjWQ9PPNPC1JFxgfzkYziru86p6wnP0Lfc56HG9ATkoP3DDSLv0","answers":["to delay","been delayed","delayed","delay"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5R2ijVcdI3U4+lXLPt2d5DIjQ5UzeYhFzL47R6CwaUbh/t1L8rpugOEvnCsHP14baUbbMhN8WTtXZA1ktHuwkbH9NdcI9idlHLNY9r2y7QBzZBXadSmO4Sy/C9GJud23dWyw2HCedRb4Gz+eM9z/Ncb/rhG1YZBm+kc0BaJPspSWVUuvcmHcdFbGw4Ig2hPbE1E92ZJeaeVcUlS90NAHbMvlzVpdnD5TfPNPxCgjpW8Oo/16/nT3834nH3/RxIFzIgYuz8jXBy/zX6mZvV3JMg159cEe6I0eBopmt8AWprr1T8oAcwzSlZSc+FJkgrHrwqeL6Ik4QW3XRrj9RAiBXrIVG2XNLLUoGvkJKbebLjBOIjdFn4CeFNCIYDINpmS/KYw1T/2o+iBv1+CULmde+2nPR2ZHHToKBzWNAMYASNW0q1Hr4uQB+G3gbil1Yi/Pnl9m9CLLl3HvbM9uc+m3Fioa9VSgjjjczov0o9mRumQoCzGaHXWDGCdEemh9w2PmhXDW19b9/c4N/J+IdlH4Vk\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17045","langCode":"vi","question":"eOvx8vaZXnawPteIScTLGW0+ZXSg9S6UOPuG+5pN60U7iN4G5qHWXyQmIRuPJM0I","answers":["been paid","paid","pay","be paid"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1oMoZ8byV8R35cdIzN/OTCYHwJi9NikancPb3zzjOYFaLwZymj2qU6IBhMrqbYzPiLNnZM1YCpK2Lne+VP8KTN2at6RfVtf6mlLoK0dt2iFKvvTxaVOiE/5Hjjq6QQbmtHWmDFRGRVOZ3r96QwZG9FIEywo0BAziFXXCZmFh1TGWVUuvcmHcdFbGw4Ig2hPbE1E92ZJeaeVcUlS90NAHbMvlzVpdnD5TfPNPxCgjpW8Oo/16/nT3834nH3/RxIFzIgYuz8jXBy/zX6mZvV3JMgHXGt+90cLPPIlFDKUZbggIeHfPTFA/qeebIkWrNPiENCW1U89ndBkUYqP7hH3HfegP7VRNTk7Vt9pLxslreofvalwj82hIDQszdXFjUA30V5hYgG9d4MJB/kYuo7HH+TjnAOvho+VpnAMSz6/IXT8NTio13BG2CZN2RaGCDszf/fX9k2hZT2Y9nkNYlhE9PexaKzLDRwney9dNOANIY4JpB6PqqVzfHRcLC0DKMuZGR79ggiCA2AobdGaalRdjQi6bh2SH55O/x9rBeT1dDgB"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17046","langCode":"vi","question":"sMcqzQqSnA69tYRBsvKHzPdwbTxJIBxspUd21L2+0zyehFy0Rp+zM2j6YYi9r5W8","answers":["finished","been finished","finish","be finished"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4bfU/CEyJIFVYMamug/fZ6rC5a7LUL57RwuKA9Hn4OeQgVvub1EUpKGW9cNW4pHMIbQfpzV9mlL0ggFFGsf1Ee8RF/5Pk3zd8B9chLqVs7h2Zi+OWh+6PFZ44qWC4nxNlHE5/OwXjAt1+X9EBh6c20UD8X9iLfoATkgUpcLWqrHL0KmK4z3T7iXFwAooPrDRpuad2Iq0K5HegxsODWHW5kGDUhAAVTnnprOfdyMOD3Eq345v8xT1MhV/qwT/QRoJ6JDk0KJ1OE+qKH8M+ewGVv6kzs+wfq7bW+QHxVYGkanRQ/NhMWfgHbzEtE3fMBPGcrMgwEXn4TjzX/KFnwi/PbRBaFB7It/SseQQHAv0Zrjza9tCkHqBTeXlJ2xlgTbWVmjNhZvjhzSub3JIck5J9XAXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8bzlX2DEdQOujWweqxjQzPX5fm3IZdhL/YEs3zm/Xw53a654X4ZNErq7hDCp6wFujpS0PzPU5J+fjvEOlO+qYza+J2D3EUE/qgZY26VnvdJc"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17047","langCode":"vi","question":"8LjKm7q0i1O3uXaIXyIBCMXC4TqaCzh/7rxOMY0cFFpGSV0QO9/6WSK6p3z8xsJ2XSKhgWTV/PdchdEEM0D8BA\u003d\u003d","answers":["to be finished","been finished","be finished","finished"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4yh6oYXrjsmEQAyiVypqJReNF1sB2VeE7NDhNwYcMiEAlx6DgIsht5q1F74byIyYstJ0IUWJaUAKWqknA8IXsoYpKmW+XGzpnrkQ/JTWSUEGUrIirmealKptAx7TgKbZ+RhPwnTZE0IUEmdlRbL4voNsVgUldsvEKnQOopH1HoaohbsZ6dk73CBmDY+DGZP1hY2iwUK3Z/aZZh989SPM5Tx3jJpeTlAniFwAkWBgOS5vJ6dnI2kR0wUlZhOLJOeN+y5u8xj6TRupjRGj47vDPMgSBvgX1kqkX6L1WAN/SwhLy0kn331ESzxOEZ05dd9dmJOdHjfhykEUSSYwBGqQeV/ip5tYdqLr7hvMWkSJjk4rjbTh6uCfZVs+z+32JutTdq4xGoHMdn21g1mbw0Fa39FJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfUZ5W9M3Kn7zyQedlKP4a6tOA1WuEcJjgwpCYplmcf/t9nDOedoZaHA5y2xddLfNjALRNIz1bZ/lPeE8Ij7K+UmtdkVOIw8hnpdBB4+MG/SKhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17048","langCode":"vi","question":"twjydX5T0wSf2opDIKwFLHLJDvJDdrsJ4LWINqJ6QgM\u003d","answers":["to been immature","be immature","to be immature","is immature"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEw0gw4aeJvYMfe9MgQZyOtNQqlC3Dk6yXjcyvswb1pPVAlx6DgIsht5q1F74byIyYqQTAqCIK328THRnbE+WHqKMZYzamuasz1AA+V2hExCteBUux2iOcjU8gSSb8xX2FvDEfROag7Yl+BnLJmZNFRjGCGr4hDqxp+xy47LzjiSrM+OSdcnZC0gCTUXWq80xzBJ+rjOWTi4j1gl3o9hlJZpb/z97GduX8nGacT1GBlduburK6cOH55bAOxJIMl1BpKlycXuaPzDlY+j376wUO2etUsrXVnjo12uzCsBei1QC4QkGcCB9neqrglDBfaDFmNacsKroHNRSHbmUrgN1lVwOfVIEqltF7+hrgmV8yGs9I4dpo1gEfxc6Qn9uqqjFfc+9xm8cWKfOWeDs4VYQJ0g79B2LFS0++yD1BmOLjp0jv4PuoObCzI7USPID4HQhasZNiAyCCrt8b8InI5g+8f5+dhWNxeYP628UjjTBOuONxp3rDYoV7mKjrrQYz/Owkr9pe2f1JfYvzJq4JuN+ryDXj10iMCpIQLb09QEsQtv019tj79GH2z3w/QGMK4n+H9qxOUQnrt9WOKnYo8x6IgfQwYsW/DBZirrbPMzi8SvgMlD6uBVOiBPAYGAL4SKJU3Bg5oS5Wz0VO2ncBMF26kxwEQmG7NqeKh3vn20vC2lvXhcGik0Qr8HAnTDBlnEGwkUnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59iRPQPgP5WqhHghE6qO6MFOO5G8Tpkzn0cISFMEhzL1kgrd1QSLZqNOIyvUgR8NQzmVOcQsVVz2uhZgqelSBj6g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"17","id":"17049","langCode":"vi","question":"TdD20cmKjVUxnzXoQ7nJPkX4LYdSyKuqUE272iDnnbnufYkYQ4MGiV7dGc1e/oPy","answers":["is","be","to be","been"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2VB2i/r8nIdodzMbbAoMAXoCakykRhx2BqQyumPdnOndXiShHg/FCnZ7ltbE11YfsjEcjksvkip3WTND7M6hydpPgBFDLtgjOI41l0jiR9nOBCW+wJnYWLnCy7ByYl/aEcbUwIrJmzzDD1JbJEWpvZZqNXiKZKlz4ltSsdEawYl/cuWkkKwkB6DOhAn5HE+MHVHoN/fwkmC6/OroIucg0qMZYzamuasz1AA+V2hExCteBUux2iOcjU8gSSb8xX2FsMs7a1J5DKEADbMFhs1f3kvYhf8++9SHaUsyLPr7x4fLaf5Yy8+sD6tk+Bmyknu04N60s4cdS/2/1Y2SOj77HvGnesNihXuYqOutBjP87CSXMiIqIbRbIH58tnZEnxYFIjQjDLyQovBj2JwG/dqR7ObCh+FiT53OVU5XVtB12Gmnb02SWWyBMHkIk7xdkEqcJ2XjUGT8dRgHWOxy9RY7OJEsRqQfLajKXGVLzW5UmrmFLjrrBQwoQFq1liXofYiOdePXSIwKkhAtvT1ASxC2/TX22Pv0YfbPfD9AYwrif4fX24xISAEmCqvQ4/ATRvSuXKQEYSiF4H6jcVgpOZWeT6U8BA8jqBHyujyAqEbq3YwN9PoV72aIzahbTw5HDI6RlZQuvz+yyD/rB2zjBv+1B1sOcqFZrpkri7bf6VV9q8xOuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU21Xxl+iKlQVrDebKi78ffNLXs95IBlpGVe5OvrXWNCYjstSIwhvQMxCJkQLQ0kYhmV8vdi1neWdnOzTgQ32I3Nva3b3UBqXColLIbbTT5Df6A\u003d\u003d"}]